<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!--format:
<text>
	<paragraph>
		<type> (primary, secondary)</type>
		<body>(blah blah blah)</body>
	</paragraph>
	
	<paragraph> 
		etc...
	</paragraph>
</text>
!-->

<text>

	<paragraph>
		<type>primary</type>
		<body>The Little Man</body>
	</paragraph>
	
	<paragraph>
		<type>secondary</type>
		<body>Once upon a time there was a tiny little man. He was so small that he could ride on the backs of the larger cockroaches. You know,those big ones that are all disgusting? The kinds that you run away from. But the little man was not scared of these cockroaches, because they liked him. He was always nice to them, and  they would let him ride on their backs. He always washed them off with a tiny piece of cloth his mother gave him when he was younger though, because cockroaches are not clean by nature. But they are much nicer than you might expect. The point is, this man was very little.</body>
	</paragraph>

	<paragraph>
		<type>secondary</type>
		<body>When he was a little child, the little man used to feel sorry for himself. And why shouldn't he have? I would venture to say that you'd feel at least a little sorry too, being as small as he was. One day, he ran home in the middle of the school day. His eyes were raining tears, and his heart had sunk into his stomach. When his mother came home, she heard the pathetic sound of a faint wimper coming from the little child's room. She opened the door, and saw him on his tiny little desk, crying big big tears.</body>
	</paragraph>

	<paragraph>
		<type>secondary</type>
		<body>"What's wrong, my little angel?" said Mother, who picked up the little boy and nestled him in her big soft hands. She listened as he explained his big problem, "Today--at school--I got thirsty. So I had my teacher pick me up, so I could drink from the water fountain. But a big kid came by and made the water flow out fast. I couldn't breathe. I thought I was going to die. And then the water started towards the drain, taking me with it. I tried to swim, but I couldn't escape the drain. I grabbed the edge, just in time. Emily found me there, screaming like a little girl." The little boy had a little crush on Emily. "A bunch of kids laughed at me after that. So I got sad and I ran home." He looked up at Mother.</body>
	</paragraph>
	
	<paragraph>
		<type>secondary</type>
		<body>Mother did not speak for a while. It was easy to tell that she worried for her little man. But after a while, she bent down and gave him a big hug. She said something that the little man would never forget, "My little pumpkin," she said sweetly, "you should be sad. But not for yourself. Can't you see how jealous all of the other children are? You get to take rides on butterflies. Do any of the other children climb daisys? No, because when they try, they only crush them." The little boy let the beginnings of a big smile take shape on his little face. "You see my little prince, it might be true that there are things that other children can do that you cannot. But never forget that you can do so much that nobody else can." And with a kiss and a hug, Mother left the room.</body>
	</paragraph>

	<paragraph>
		<type>secondary</type>
		<body>When the little boy went to school the next day, he sat on a clover to think. As he was thinking, he started tying tiny blades of grass into tiny little knots. He didn't even notice what he was doing until Emily bent down to say, "Oh how beautiful! Is that for me?" Looking down at the grass, he realized that he had woven the grass into a big-people sized necklace, enscribed with the name "Emily." Soon, every girl wanted the little artist to make them a necklace. The boys wanted him to teach them how he did it, so that they could impress the girls too.</body>
	</paragraph>
	
	<paragraph>
		<type>secondary</type>
		<body>That little boy became a little man. Every day, he gets up, and rides a cockroach to the front door--after wiping it off of course. Cockroaches are very dirty by nature. He goes outside, and he feels a little sorry for all the big men out there, who never got to fly on the backs of butterflys.</body>
	</paragraph>
</text>
